bizchannel.com.my 2006-10-08

# BizChannel - Privacy Policy

| 

| ****|   
---|---|---  
WE FIRMLY BELIEVE THAT THE PRIVACY OF OUR CUSTOMERS' INFORMATION IS FUNDAMENTAL TO SECURING PUBLIC TRUST AND CONFIDENCE IN OUR PRODUCTS AND SERVICES AND THEREFORE, IT IS OUR POLICY TO RESPECT, MAINTAIN, PROTECT AND SAFEGUARD, AT ALL TIMES, THE PRIVACY OF OUR CUSTOMERS' INFORMATION UNDER THE [WWW.BIZCHANNEL.COM.MY](http://www.bizchannel.com.my/) WEBSITE WHICH IS OPERATED BY US AT BUMIPUTRA-COMMERCE BANK BERHAD.   
   
1. | Introduction  
  |   | 

We have always considered our Customers and their interests as being of utmost priority in the provision of our products and services. For this reason and others, we are committed to ensuring that the privacy of your personal, banking and financial information as well as any other information in respect of or pertaining to the same ("Information") which you have disclosed, shared, exchanged or otherwise provided to us is at all times respected, maintained, protected and safeguarded. 

Pursuant thereto and for your benefit, this Privacy Policy (which we may amend from time to time) is designed to explain and elaborate upon some of our policies and principles pertaining to the privacy of your Information, all of which we have adopted as a sign of our commitment to respecting, maintaining, protecting and safeguarding the privacy of your Information.   
  
  |    
2. | Types Of Information Which We Collect  
  | The types of Information, which we collect, varies depending upon how you access and use our products and services. Nevertheless, the Information which we collect generally comprises of data and information pertaining to yourself such as your name, age, gender, race, National Registration Identification Card (NRIC) No. as well as other financial and banking information such as your bank balance, bank transactions, assets, liabilities, income and creditworthiness, and where the Customer is a company, information pertaining to its assets, liabilities, directors, officers, shareholders and financial and commercial dealings.   
  |    
3. | Use Of The Information  
  | The Information, which we gather from you, is generally meant to be used in the ordinary course of our business including the provision of our products and services to you as requested. However, our use of your Information may also extend to other purposes, among others, to enforce or defend any of our rights, to comply with all applicable legislation, laws and regulations, to enhance the quality of our products and services, to prevent fraud or illegal activities as well as to prepare demographics_new concerning our Customers' use of our products and services which may, at our sole discretion, be made available to our third party vendors, advertisers, affiliates or relevant third parties in aggregate or demographic form.   
  |    
4. | Employees' Access To The Information  
  | We repeat our commitment to respect, maintain, protect and safeguard the privacy of your Information by ensuring that any access to the Information which you have disclosed, shared, exchanged or otherwise provided to us is restricted to our duly authorised employees, all of which are fully trained and well-equipped to handle your Information. Each of our said duly authorised employees is required to adhere to our commitment herein specifically our dedication to safeguarding the privacy of your Information at all times. Failure by our respective duly authorised employees herein to comply with the same and generally the terms of this Privacy Policy shall be met with utmost strict disciplinary action.   
  |    
5. | Security Measures Employed To Safeguard The Privacy Of The Information  
  | 

It is our policy to ensure that adequate and stringent security controls, measures and protocols are employed to safeguard the privacy of your Information, all of which shall continue even after whatever contractual relationship between you and us has come to an end. While we shall use our best efforts to ensure that the privacy of all Information is kept secure, it is an accepted fact that no data transmission conducted over the Internet can be guaranteed to be wholly secure. Accordingly, we discourage you from transmitting any Information, the contents of which being confidential or sensitive, to us via the Internet as we are unable to guarantee the privacy or security of the same, unless otherwise stated. Further thereto, we shall neither be held responsible nor liable for any damages or losses which you may suffer, whether directly or indirectly, as a result of the said Information being stolen, tampered with, copied, abused, misused or otherwise violated. 

Further information on the security controls, measures and protocols, which we have employed herein, are specified and elaborated upon in our SECURITY ARRANGEMENT, which we trust you will read and understand.   
  
  |    
6. | Sharing Of Information  
  | 

We shall, at all times, endeavour to safeguard the privacy of your Information and accordingly, we do not disclose the same to any third party or external organisations. Notwithstanding this and for the purposes of helping us serve you better, your non-banking and non-financial information may be provided to our third party vendors, advertisers, affiliates or relevant third parties subject to your consenting to the same. Further thereto, where such non-banking and non-financial information is provided to these entities, we shall take all reasonable efforts to ensure that they comply with the same standards regulating the privacy of your Information as that which is imposed by us. Nevertheless, should you wish at anytime to withdraw your consent and you do not want your non-banking and non-financial information being further disclosed to these entities or do not want to be solicited for further products or services which are offered by us or them, please notify us accordingly via electronic-mail or post at the contact addresses as specified in Item 9 below. 

Notwithstanding the generality of this Privacy Policy and while we shall, at all times, endeavour to safeguard the privacy of your Information, we may nevertheless disclose your Information to other entities where such disclosure:- 

| i. | is requested or authorised by you;   
---|---  
ii. |  is used for the purposes of completing, verifying or restricting any transaction made by you;   
iii. | 

is made to the Central Credit Unit established by Bank Negara Malaysia pursuant to its request;   
  
iv. | is made to verify the existence and conditions of your Account(s) for a third party such as a credit bureau or merchant;   
v. |  is lawfully permitted or required;  
vi. |  is in compliance with any judicial order or legal requirement;  
vii. | 

is required to protect and defend us and our property; and   
  
viii. |  is required to protect the interests of the public including but not limited to the detection of crimes and the apprehension of criminals.   
  |    
7. | Customer's Choices In Respect Of The Provision Of The Information  
  | While you are neither bound nor obligated to provide us with any of your Information, your choice not to do so (whether due to your disagreement with the methods employed by us to safeguard the privacy of your Information or otherwise) may result in you being prohibited from accessing or making full use of our products and services, neither of which shall render us responsible or liable for.   
  |    
8. | Accuracy Of The Information  
  | 

We acknowledge that the accuracy of your Information provided to us is essential, among others, to the provision of our products and services to you. Accordingly, it would be in your best interests to ensure that whatever Information which you provide to us is, at all times, accurate, complete, current and true. 

For this purpose, you are encouraged to help us maintain accurate records of your Information by notifying us of any changes to the same so that we may amend or update your Information where necessary. Should you also have any other queries concerning your Information or its accuracy, please inform us accordingly. Any such notification or queries can be made by contacting our Call Center or e-mailing us, at the contact number and address as specified under Item 9 below.   
  
  |    
9. | Questions Or Complaints About This Privacy Policy  
  | 

We, at all times, welcome and encourage you to raise any questions or complaints which you may have concerning this Privacy Policy. For this purpose, please do not hesitate to contact our Call Centre:- 

**BCB Call Center**  
10th Floor, Menara Atlas   
Plaza Pantai, Off Jalan Pantai Baru   
59200 Kuala Lumpur   
Wilayah Persekutuan  
Malaysia.  
TEL. : 1-300-880-900 / (+603) 2295-6100  
FAX. : (+603) 2288-1653 & 2288-1654   
E-MAIL : [b](mailto:bizchannel@corpmail.bcb.com.my)[izchannel@corpmail.bcb.com.my ](mailto:bizchannel@corpmail.bcb.com.my)  

  |   | Copyright 2001   
Bumiputra-Commerce Bank Berhad  |
